CAREER PROFILE

My name is Konstantinos Sventzouris and i graduated from the school of Electical and Computer Engineering. For the last 10 years i have been working in a Company that constructs and supports fuel stations as a manager of the integrated system of management of input and output of Gas Stations I am the quality manager of the company's laboratory according to ISO 17025 I have developed a tank volume measurement software. In 2022 i have decided to undertake the Hellenic Open University's master degree in Pervasive and Mobile Computing Systems



EXPERIENCES

Manager of Intergated system of I/O of Gas Stations IKAROS S.A. 2013 - Present

- Support and management of Intergrated system of Management of Input and Output Of Gas Stations
- Development of Software for tank volume measument
- Quality Control Manager of the Laboratory
- Customer Support for POS systems

IT support

2008 - 2012

Freelancer

- IT support for Customers
- Server Administration



SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

Fortran

C

C++

Communication

organizational



Konstantinos Sventzouris

Developer

- std162798@ac.eap.gr (mailto:std162798@ac.eap.gr)
- **J** 012 345 6789 (tel:012 345 6789)
- Europe/Athens Timezone ()
- konssven.github.io (http://konssven.github.io)
- Konssven (http://github.com/Konssven)
- Resume PDF (https://konssven.github.io/assets/pdf/C)

EDUCATION

MSc in Pervasive and Mobile Computing Systems

Hellenic Open University of Greece 2022 - Present

BSc in Electrical and Computer Engineering

Democritus University of Thrace 2003 - 2010

LANGUAGES

Greek (Native)

English (Professional)

| Problem Analysis | |
|------------------|---------------------|
| | INTERESTS |
| | Reading |
| | Traditional Dancing |
| | Watching Series |
| | |